声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：e0yue
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
帮我找封信好么...是留着等我来取的
I'm expecting a letter."Hold for guest arrival."
-好的  你叫什么?  -Joan Hart
-Sure. What's your name?  -Joan Hart.
Joan Hart
白金版
Platinum.
白金版?
Platinum?
就像白金版唱片一样
As in platinum record.
就是有百万销量的那种
As in a million units sold.
现在  当大家知道我在空难中死了以后
Now, Drive Shaft's albums must've...
主动轴乐队的专辑大概就会滞销了
...spiked when everybody found out that I died in some catastrophic plane disaster.
但是当我活着...
But when I come back?
回去以后...
Alive!
那肯定会很疯狂
It's gonna be insane.
那么你认为那个救生艇有用了?
So you think the raft's gonna work?
当然它很有用  看看那个东西
Of course. Look at that thing.
那不是救生艇  他们造的是一艘船
It's not a raft. They built a sodding boat.
当他们获救的时候  直升飞机就会来的
When they get picked up, the helicopters will come,
这会让我们看起来很难以置信  并且会因此出名的
making us ridiculously and eternally famous.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
你不想出名么?
Don't you want to be famous?
你看看那边发生了什么?
What do you think's going on over there?
当然  如果你们不想死的话
Sure. You can absolutely wait a few weeks before you launch.
你们绝对应该等到几周后再出发
I was just assuming you didn't want to die.
那么  我们下一次能在什么时候出发?
So, uh, when's the next time we can launch?
3个...
Three...
可能是4个月吧
maybe four months.
好了  就算是电视里的气象员也不能准确预测天气
Come on! Even a weatherman on TV don't know what's gonna happen.
我们为什么要听Arzt的?
Why are we listening to Arzt?
因为我是一个博士  而你只是一个山里的农民
Because I'm a doctor and you're a hillbilly.
你是一个混蛋的高中理科老师
You're a damn high school science teacher.
Sawyer  让他说下去
Hey, Sawyer, let's just let the man talk.
这些天来每天下午都下雨
It's been raining every afternoon.
这就是说我们正处在季风季节快要来的时候
That means that we are on the cusp of monsoon season.
季风季节是很不利的
Monsoon season is bad.
现在  信风正在向北面吹
Now, the trade winds are blowing north right now.
行船的方向是向北的
Shipping lanes are north.
北面才是你们真正想去的
So north is exactly where you want to be.
那说明了什么?
What's that mean?
那是说当季风季节来的时候
It means, when the monsoon season hits,
信风会转而向南方吹
the trade winds are gonna shift to the south.
救生艇是顺着风向走的
The raft goes with the wind.
有人知道我们南面唯一的陆地是哪个么?
Can anyone tell me what is the only piece of land that's south of us?
南极洲
Antarctica.
说对了Jack  南极洲
That's right, Jack. Antarctica.
那么我们应该什么时候走?
So when do we have to leave?
昨天
Yesterday.
那么很明显你是相信他了?
So obviously you believe him.
Arzt?  我不知道  但是我是不会放弃任何机会的
Arzt? I don't know. But I'm not taking any chances.
你认为你明天前能准备好么?
You think you'll be ready by tomorrow?
那人说没一天可以浪费了
Man said not a day to waste.
补给都备好了?   你准备了食物  淡水...
Supplies all set? You got food, fresh water, every...
Kate别冲动  但是我有事要做
Look, Kate, no offense, but I got work to do.
为什么突然这么感兴趣?
Why the sudden interest?
因为我要和你一起走
Because I'm going with you.
迷 失
第一季 第二十二集
救生艇满了  我们只能载四个人 而人已经齐了
Look, raft's full. We need four, we got four.
-包括Sawyer么?  -是的
-Including Sawyer?  -Including him.
我们需要他的东西  所以他用他的东西换来了他的船票
We needed the stuff he had, so he bought his way on.
在第一个已经被烧了的救生艇上
On the first raft, which burned.
我不来跟你辩理  我告诉过他...
I'm not gonna get into semantics. I told the guy...
他甚至不知道怎么航海
He doesn't know how to sail.
那么你知道?
And you do?
我在喷气船上当了两年的船员  我知道在帆船上该怎么做
I spent two summers crewing Jlboats. I know my way around a sailboat.
也许是这样...  但是交易就是交易
Yeah... maybe so, but a deal's a deal. I'm sorry.
你也带Walt么?
You're bringing Walt too?
我刚说了那是很危险的
I'm just saying it's dangerous.
我来决定怎么保护我孩子的安全
I decide what's best for my boy.
现在对他来说最好的事就是离开这个该死的岛了
And right now, what's best for him is to get the hell off this island.
救生艇已经满了
The raft's full.
我有快递给Diane Jansen
I have a delivery for Diane Jansen.
她刚从重点护理组出来  她在208房间
She just came up from ICU. She's in room 208.
好的
Okay.
在你右边的拐角处
Around the corner, to your right.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Thanks.  -You're welcome.
Tom
Katie
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
Diane得了癌症快死了
Diane's dying of cancer.
虽然我还欠着她没去看她
I thought I owed it to her to come see her.
我听说了  我很难过
I heard. I'm sorry.
是的  我也是
Yeah, me too.
那么你坐在我车的后面有什么特殊的原因么?
So any particular reason why you're hanging out in the back of my car?
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
你也要走么?
拜托了Jin  说说话
是的  我也要走
还有多远?
How much further?
快到了
We're almost there.
可以告诉我我们去哪儿了吧  Sayid
Wanna tell me where we're going, Sayid?
你最好还是自己看看
It's better that you see it for yourself.
不  我不是太肯定
No, I'm not so sure it is.
告诉我你为什么把我带到这儿来  不然我就回去了
Tell me why you brought me here or I turn around.
是我叫他把你带到这儿来的
He brought you out here because I asked him to.
我叫他别和你说
I asked him not to tell you.
我希望你虚心一点
I wanted you to have an open mind.
对什么虚心一点?
Open mind about what?
天那
My God.
-这是什么东西?  -正是那个东西
-What is this thing?  -Exactly.
我想是时间我们谈谈这个了
I guess it's time we talked about this.
长官
Yo, chief!
有几个问题
Dumb question here.
我们是要在海上航行  是么?
We're sailing out on the ocean right?
你认为呢?
You mind?
这个苏禄人打理的手提箱里尽是腌鱼
Sulu over here is packing a suitcase full of salted fish.
那又怎么?
Yeah?
我们不能抓鱼么?
We can't catch fish?
你知道多少在海上的生存知识?
Do you know anything about surviving at sea?
航行?  驾驶?  掌舵?
Sailing? Navigating? Steering a raft?
你会么?
Do you?
不管我知不知道  船是我造的
Doesn't matter what I know, I built it.
也许让你上救生艇是一个错误
Maybe you are the wrong guy to go on the raft.
你要踢掉我是么  米基?
You gonna vote me off, Mickey?
那么哪个顶替我的是哪个混蛋?
And who the hell's gonna take my place?
你以为你在做什么混账事?
What the hell you think you're doing?
别装作你不知道
Don't give me the "Aw, golly" eyes.
Michael刚刚跟我说了你骗取了我上救生艇的名额
Michael just told me you were jockeying for my spot on the raft.
我只是问了几个问题  他肯定是误解我了
I was just asking some questions. He must've misunderstood me.
我知道你在做什么
I know what you're doing.
-是么?  -是的
-Yeah?  -Yeah.
就像我知道你为什么这么想要拿回Haliburton证件
Just like I know why you wanted that Haliburton case so bad.
那个属于和我们坐同一架飞机的美国军官的东西
The one that belonged to the U.S. Marshal who was flying with us.
-你是他的犯人  -放开我
-You were his prisoner.  -Let go of me.
唯一逃跑的机会就是上救生艇  不是么?
Your only chance of running's getting on that raft, ain't it?
我们会被一艘船救起
If we get picked up by a ship,
而后回来营救剩下的那些人
when they come back to rescue the rest of y'all,
你的名字旁就会有一颗漂亮的大星号
gonna be a nice big asterisk next to your name.
亲爱的  别担心
Well, don't worry, puddin',
你的秘密我会帮你保守的
your secret's safe with me.
但是你也要知道
But just so you know,
你绝对别想取代我的位置上救生艇
no way in hell you're getting my spot on that raft.
Sawyer
Hey, Sawyer!
我要那个名额
I want your spot,
我会替代你的名额的
I'll get your spot.
伙计  给我瓶水
Give me that water, man.
给你  爸爸
Yo, Dad!
谢谢
Thanks.
你刚才在和Sawyer吵什么?
So, what were you and Sawyer arguing about?
我向他说了一些他不想听的事
I told him something he didn't want to hear.
为什么他那么想上救生艇?
Why does he wanna get on the raft so much?
因为他知道上这艇他就会获救的
Cause he knows it's gonna work.
当我们获救时
When we get rescued,
我们会回来营救剩下的那些人的  对么?
we're gonna come back for everybody else, right?
是的  那是当然了
Yeah. Sure. Of course.
但是有件事
But the thing is...
这个岛...
this island...
是...  想再找到它有点难
is... finding it again might be hard.
我们能坐飞机来找么?
Can't we fly around and look for it?
当然可以
Absolutely.
但是还不能保证能找到  这就是为什么你和...
But there's no guarantees. That's why you and...
爸爸?
Dad?
这就是为什么你...
That's why you...
爸爸
Dad!
叫Jack来
Get Jack.
帮帮忙
Help!
我需要帮忙  我爸爸不对了
I need help! It's my dad.
-怎么了?  -他的胃很痛
-What's the matter?  -His stomach is really bad.
把他带回Michael那儿  我去找Jack
Take him back to Michael. I'll go get Jack.
-好的  我们快走  -往这边
-Okay. Let's go.  -This way.
Jack
你发现这个多久了?
How long have you known about this?
3周吧  差不多是的
Three weeks, give or take.
3周了
Three weeks.
你来这儿挖这个东西已经有3周了
You've been out here for three weeks digging this thing up
而你却从没和我说起过?
and you never told me?
尊敬的Jack  什么时候我向你汇报事情过了?
All due respect, Jack, but since when do I report to you?
尊敬的John  你说谎了
All due respect, John, but you lied.
在你决定和大家说之前
How long did you have that case full of guns
你有一整箱的枪这个秘密你保守了多久了?
before you decided the rest of us needed to know?
你有你自己的判断力  我有我的
You used your best discretion. I used mine.
-那么我们怎么才能打开它?  -什么?
-So how do we open it?  -What?
你想打开它?
You want to open it?
是的
Yeah.
我们应该埋了它
We should bury it.
我带你来是为了让你劝他离开这个疯狂的东西
I brought you here to talk him out of this insanity.
里面可能会有任何东西
Anything could be inside.
最好的想法是  里面有补给资源
Best case scenario, there's supplies.
最坏的也只是我们把它当遮蔽物来用
Worst case, we use it as a shelter.
Jack  事实上我能想到比那更坏的事
Actually, Jack, I can think of much worse cases than that.
你注意到这个舱门的一些问题了么?
You notice anything about this hatch?
没有把手
There's no handle.
原因已经再明显不过了
Could the reason for that be more obvious?
可能本来它就不打算让人从外面打开
Maybe it was never meant to be opened from the outside.
Jack
我在这儿
Yeah! Over here!
是Michael  有点不对劲
It's Michael. Something's wrong.
你今天吃了什么?
What'd you eat today?
水果...  鱼
Fruit, fish.
喝了足够的水了么?
Drinking enough water?
两三瓶吧
Two, three bottles.
你从哪儿打来的水?
Where are you getting that water from?
和其它人一样  山洞里打的
The caves, like everybody else.
好的  听着Michael...
All right, listen, Michael.
放松一下  好么?
You just take it easy.
呆在阴凉的地方  尽量不要乱动
You stay in the shade. You try not to move too much, Okay?
我们得在明天启航  必须要
We have to launch that raft tomorrow. We have to.
我知道  我要你躺回去
I know. I need you to lay back.
躺下吧
Lay down.
躺下  好么?
Just lay down. Okay?
Adam
听我说  你能凑出点时间来帮我做核磁共振么?
listen, can you carve out some time for me on the MRI?
是的  是帮我一个朋友的朋友的忙
Yeah, it's... it's a favor for a friend of a friend.
-不 那可以解决的  -好的  谢谢 Adam
-No, that'll work out great.  -Okay. Yeah, thanks, Adam.
他叫Connor
His name's Connor.
-几岁了?  -下周就满22个月了
-How old is he?  -Twenty-two months next week.
他真的很漂亮
He's beautiful.
那多亏了Rachel  不是我
Yeah, well, that's Rachel, that's not me.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
她去Cedar Rapids探望亲属了
She's over in Cedar Rapids visiting her folks.
周日才回来
They get back on Sunday.
我叫Diane来做核磁共振了
I got Diane in for an MRI.
他们会把她带到楼下的X射线科的
They'll bring her downstairs to radiology.
约定是在早上的5点  那么...
And her appointment's not until 5 am,
我们还有3小时的时间
so we've got about three hours to kill.
-Tom...  -不客气
-Tom...  -You're welcome.
你想它还在哪儿么?
You think it's still there?
什么?
What?
你知道的
You know what.
现在是午夜啊  Katie
It's the middle of the night, Katie.
我们不会再有机会了
We might not get another chance.
1  2  3  4  5... 6
One, two, three, four, five, six.
你认为他怎么了  中暑?
What do you think it is? Heatstroke?
不  他感到那是突然痛起来的
No. He would've felt that coming on.
也许是坏水果?  生吃的鱼?
Bad fruit, maybe? Raw fish?
Michael和Jin吃的东西是一样的
Michael and Jin are on the same diet.
-并且Jin没事  -Jin没事
-And Jin's fine.  -Jin's fine.
不管怎么样他的病痛是突然袭来的
Whatever's making him sick was metabolized fast.
得病很快  而且很痛苦
It hit him quick, and it hit him hard.
那么你认为是那瓶水了?
So you think it was the water?
不  我不认为是因为水
No, I don't think it was the water.
我认为是因为水里面的东西
I think it was something in the water.
感觉好点了么?
Feeling any better?
腹部的绞痛平息下来了
Cramps are quieting down.
只要我不动或是
As long as I don't move,
或是呼吸
or breathe.
你和Locke和好了么?
You and Locke kiss and make up?
好的
Good.
-不 Michael  -什么?
-No, Michael.  -What?
喝这儿的
Drink from that one.
-有人暗算我?  -我不知道
-Somebody did this to me?  -I don't know.
我还不能肯定
I'm not sure of anything yet.
Sawyer
我的任务是抗竹子  但是有时是我去灌水的
I'm on bamboo duty, but sometimes I help refill the water.
Michael和Jin相处得好么?
Michael and Jin getting along?
他们一起造救生艇  吵架时也像是一对结了婚的夫妻
They fight like a married couple building a raft together.
你和他说了?
You told him?
他认为可能是Sawyer干的
He thinks Sawyer might've done it.
是因为Kate么?
'cause of Kate?
Kate
是的  我猜她想上救生艇
Yeah, I guess she wants on the raft.
所以Sawyer暗算Michael  因为你知道他决定谁上艇
So Sawyer went off on Michael because he gets to decide who goes.
你们不会认为是Kate干的吧  是么?
You don't think Kate did it?
Kate为什么向Michael下毒?
Why would Kate poison Michael?
你知道  整个逃亡的事
Well, you know, the whole fugitive thing.
他不知道
He doesn't know?
我怎么能知道这边上谁不知道
How am I supposed to keep straight who knows what?
我是说Steve甚至连北极熊的事也不知道
Steve didn't know about the polar bear.
她做了什么?
What did she do?
我不知道  你为什么不去问她?
I don't know. Why don't you ask her?
你认为其它人不需要知道这个么  Jack?
You didn't think the others should know about this, Jack?
判断力  John
Discretion, John.
好了 你能不要动么 我会把你的耳朵减下来的
Okay, can you stop moving or I'm gonna cut your ear off.
这很好
This is good.
我又在写歌了  我真的感觉很好
I'm writing again. I'm really feeling it, as well.
那么...  当你获救后你会做得第一件事是什么?
So, what's the first thing you're gonna do when we get rescued?
你知道  事实上我还不知道
You know, I don't really know.
你能在洛杉矶和我闲逛
You can hang out with me in LA.
你和你孩子
You and Turnip Head.
你知道  直到你了解到什么
You know, until you figure things out.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了  听听这首吧  这是第二首
Okay. Check this out. This is track two.
叫做...   对不起
It's called... Sorry.
叫做"怪兽吃了飞行员"
It's called Monster Eats The Pilot.
Michael怎么样了?
How's Michael?
他会没事的
He's gonna be fine.
有人可以取代他上救生艇么?
Is somebody gonna be taking his place on the raft?
我不知道
I don't know.
因为你知道  Arzt博士说如果他们明天不...
Dr. Arzt said if they don't leave...
是你给Michael下的毒么  Kate?
Did you poison Michael, Kate?
他不是生病  是有人在暗算他
He's not sick. Someone did this.
你真的以为我能做到么?
Do you really think I'm capable of that?
我不知道什么是你能做到的
I don't know what you're capable of.
你带了啤酒?
You brought beer?
爱荷华州有自尊心的男人去哪儿都带着啤酒
No self-respecting man in lowa goes anywhere without beer.
这不公平  你知道
It's not fair, you know,
你回到...
you coming back.
这儿来...
Here.
家里
Home.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
看看这东西
Wow! Look at this stuff.
天那  我的飞机
Oh, my God! My plane.
我无法相信你说服我让我把这个放进这箱子
I can't believe I let you talk me into putting this in there.
那是你的主意
That was your idea.
Kate和Tom
Kate and Tom.
1989年
开始录了么?  我想还没开始吧
Is it on? I don't think it's on.
它在录了
It's on.
好的  我们是Kate Austen和Tom Brennan
Okay, uh, this is Kate Austen and Tom Brennan.
并且这是  我们为时间容器做的贡献
And this is our dedication for our time capsule
现在是1989年8月15日...
here on August 15th, 1989.
把那还给我
Hey, give me that back!
你为什么把这个傻傻的飞机放在里面呢?
Why are you putting this stupid plane in there?
因为它很酷  Katie
Because it's cool, Katie.
是我单独坐飞机去达拉斯时买的
I got it when I flew to Dallas by myself.
确实很酷  就像这个时间容器一样
Ooh, that is cool! Just like this time capsule.
当我们...比如20年后把它挖出来那会更酷
It'll be totally cool when we dig it up in, like, 20 years.
你怎么知道我们还会在一起?
How do you know we'll be together?
因为我们会结婚
'Cause we'll be married. You'll be a mom
然后你就会做妈妈  并且我们会有9个孩子
and we'll have nine kids.
我可不这么想
I don't think so.
一旦我有了驾照  我们可以开一辆车...
As soon as I get my license,
就像  你知道的私奔
we should just get in a car and drive. Like, you know, run away.
你老是想着私奔  Katie
You always wanna run away, Katie.
是的  你知道为什么
Yeah. And you know why.
事实上的结果是不是很有趣?
Funny how things turn out, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
对不起
Sorry.
我们得去医院了
We better get to the hospital.
是的
Yeah.
怎么了?
What happened?
出了点小意外
I had a little accident.
-痛么?  -是的
-Does it hurt?  -Yep.
你有事想和我说是么  Walt?
Something you wanna tell me, Walt?
不是我做的
I didn't do it.
什么不是你做的?
Didn't do what?
我听Jack说了
I heard Jack.
他认为有人暗算我爸爸
He thinks somebody got my dad sick.
不是我做的
And I didn't do it.
你以为我知道是你烧了第一艘救生艇
You think because I know you burned the first raft
就会怀疑是你让你爸中毒了?
I'd think you made your dad sick?
我们是朋友  Walt
We're friends, aren't we Walt?
我以前没有告你的密  现在我也不会这么做
I didn't tell on you before, and I'm not gonna now.
我知道你不会做任何伤害你爸爸的事的
And I know you would never do anything to hurt your dad.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
别打开它
Don't open it.
你说什么?
What did you say?
别打开它  Locke先生  别打开那个东西
Don't open it, Mr. Locke. Don't open that thing.
什么...什么东西?  你在...
What? What thing? What are you...?
只要别打开就行了
Just don't open it!
我想你大概需要这个  老板
Thought you might need that, boss.
你不会想让我们的引航员在出发之前就报销吧
Wouldn't want our pilot out of commission before takeoff.
什么  你有负罪感了?
What? You feeling guilty?
什么?
What?
你从救生艇上被除名了
You're off the raft.
再说一遍?
Come again?
你被除名了
You're off the raft.
我们有过交易
We had a deal.
是的  在你想要向我下毒的那刻起  交易就失效了
Well, the deal ended the minute you decided to poison me.
我做了什么?
I did what now?
我和你没关系了
I'm done with you.
你和我还没完
You ain't done with me by a damn sight.
你说你需要四个人
You said you needed four.
我有四个人了
I got four.
你从死尸那里偷东西
You've been stealing stuff off of dead bodies,
占为己有  用那些来买通方便
keeping it for yourself, using it to buy favors.
你是一个说谎的人  是一个罪犯
You're a liar and a criminal!
我是不会让你接近我的孩子的
I'm not letting you near my boy!
我是个罪犯  是么?
Oh, I'm a criminal?
我向你下毒因为我是个罪犯
I poisoned you 'cause I'm a criminal?
把手拿开  小子
Get your hands off me, boy.
性感臀部的小姐
Hey, sweet cheeks!
我不知道你为什么这么想离开这里
I had no idea how bad you wanted off this rock.
该是时候向大家说明了
Time to set things straight.
-告诉他谁才是罪犯  -好了 放开他 你这家伙
-Tell him who the criminal is.  -Leave her alone, man.
告诉他
Tell him.
-还给我  -离远点
-Give that back!  -Leave her alone.
看看
Look!
看看这个
Look at this.
Sawyer  不要
Sawyer, please.
你们都还记得Joanna  是吧?
You all remember Joanna, don't you?
那个淹死了的女人
The woman who drowned?
现在  看看Kate想拿可怜的Joanna的身份证做什么
Now, what's Kate doing with poor Joanna's ID?
她想上救生艇
Could it be she'd do just about anything to get on that raft,
然后获救
so she could get herself rescued?
在世界上一半的记者出现在这个混蛋的岛之前
Run off with a new identity before half the reporters in the world
以一个新的身份潜逃
descend on this damn island?
她还可能向船长下毒
She might poison the captain himself.
闭嘴
Shut up.
她不在乎别的什么  只在乎她自己
She don't care about nothing or nobody but herself.
在这儿就好了  谢谢你
This is good here. Thank you.
我的办公室就在后面  我在那儿等你
My office is right back there. I'll wait for you.
妈妈
Hi, Mom.
能听见我说话么?  妈妈?
Can you hear me? Mom?
妈妈?
Mom?
是我...Katie
It's me, Katie.
-Katherine  -是我  Katherine
-Katherine?  -It's me... Katherine.
我很抱歉让你卷入了那些事
I'm so sorry for everything that I have put you through.
救救我
Help. Help.
没事了妈妈  是我啊
It's okay, Mom. It's just me.
救命...
Help!
救命
没事的
Shh. It's okay.
救命  救命
Help! Help!
救救我
Help me!
来人  救救我
Help me! Somebody!
救救我
Help me!
救命  来人啊...
Help me! Help me!
救救我
Help me!
怎么了?
What's going on?
我是她的女儿  她有点神志不清   我要去找医生
I'm her daughter. She's confused. I was getting a doctor.
等一下
Hang on.
我们这儿有情况...
We got a situation down...
天那...
My God!
-怎么了?  -我要你车的钥匙
-What happened?  -I need your car keys.
Katie?
出去
Get out.
我不会让你这么做的  如果你合作一点  他们会...
I am not letting you do this. You cooperate, they'll go easy.
他在叫救援  出去
He's calling back-up. Get out!
-你会有个真实的生活的  -Tom  拜托了
-You can have a real life. -Tom, please.
不
No.
马上
Now!
-出去  -不
-Get out!  -No!
Tom
Tom?
天那  Tom
Oh, God. Tom!
不不不不  Tom  拜托你醒醒
No, no, no, no! Tom! Come on, please wake up.
你想告诉我们为什么你这么想逃走么?
You wanna tell us why you need to run so bad?
你想告诉我们真相么?
You wanna tell us the truth?
是的
Yes.
我在飞机上...
I was on the plane...
和一个军官在一起
with the Marshal.
是的  我被通缉了...
Yes, I was wanted...
并且被捕了...
and caught
正在被遣送回国
and being transported back.
不管我怎么说发生了什么  我应该怎么做...
No matter what I say about what happened, about what I supposedly did...
我还是会进监狱的
I'm going to jail.
但是我没有向你下毒
But I didn't poison you.
给你
Here.
-看来他是下定决心了  -是的
-He looks determined.  -Yes. He is.
你不想他走  是么?
You don't want him to go, do you?
是的  我不想
No.
这就是为什么你试图让他中毒?
Is that why you tried to make him sick?
Michael和Jin整天在一起工作
Michael and Jin working together all the time,
他们很容易把他们的水瓶搞混
pretty easy for them to get their water bottles mixed up.
我不想让他死在海上
I didn't want him to die out there.
我只是不知道该怎么办
I just didn't know what to do.
我用的剂量只能使他...
I only used enough to make him...
我不想伤害他的
I wasn't trying to hurt him.
你会告诉其他人么?
Are you gonna tell the others?
他们没理由需要知道的
I don't see any reason why they need to know.
但是  Sun...
But Sun...
他要走了
...he's going.
如果我是你  我会...
If I were you, I'd...
我会说再见
I'd say goodbye.
我又回救生艇上了
I'm back on the raft.
很替你高兴
Glad to hear it.
Michael正在打点  我们明天启航
Michael's gonna cowboy up. We set sail tomorrow.
你是来说"对不起"的么  Sawyer?
Are you here to say sorry, Sawyer?
"对不起"不像是我说的话
Sorry don't suit me.
你把我逼急了  亲爱的  我只是做我该做的
You cornered me, Freckles. I did what I had to.
我把你逼急了
I cornered you?
你说如果你想要我这个名额  你就会得到的
You said if you wanted my spot, you were gonna take it.
我想我是相信你了
Guess I believed you.
就这样了
Well... that's that.
我要整理东西去了
I got some packing to do.
为什么上那个救生艇会对你这么重要?
Why is it so important for you to be on that raft?
因为这个岛上没有什么可期望的了
'Cause there ain't anything on this island worth staying for.
一路顺风  Sawyer
Be safe, Sawyer.
肯定会的
Yeah.
-爸爸  -伙计
-Dad?  -Hey, buddy!
好点了么?
You getting better?
是的  当然马上会全好的
Yeah. Yep, I'm gonna be all right.
别担心
Hey. Don't worry.
我马上会恢复健康的
I'm gonna be on my feet soon
而且我们就要出海回家了  在你...
and we'll be sailing home before you can even...
我就是那个烧了救生艇的人
I'm the one that burned the raft.
我不想离开  我想我可以阻止你
I didn't wanna leave, and I thought I could stop you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉  爸爸
I'm really sorry, Dad.
没事的  伙计
It's okay, man.
我们能留在这儿的
We can stay here.
你和我
You and me.
我们不需要离开的
We don't have to go.
不  我们会离开的
Yes, we do.
你好
Hello.
Jack知道了
Jack knows.
我没告诉他这是你的主意
I didn't tell him it was your idea.
谢谢
Thanks.
你为什么会被惩罚?
Why should you be punished?
你只是在试着帮助我
You were only trying to help me.
他说他不会告诉其他人的
He said he wouldn't tell the others.
是的
Yeah.
Jack对保守秘密很在行
Jack's good at keeping secrets.
当我还是个小女孩...
When I was a little girl,
我相信一旦我找到我爱的男人...
I believed that once I found the man I loved...
我会很幸福的...
I would be happy...
永远
forever.
是的
Yeah.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====